myschoolgist.com.ng 2018-06-25

# Privacy Policy • Myschoolgist

At [MySchoolGist](https://www.myschoolgist.com/ "MySchoolGist"), the privacy of our visitors is of _extreme importance_ to us. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which MySchoolGist collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [https://www.myschoolgist.com](https://www.myschoolgist.com/ "MySchoolGist") website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by MySchoolGist.

### What Information do We Collect?

  *  **Personal identification information**  
We may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
  *  **Non-personal identification information**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
  *  **Web browser cookies**  
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### How We Use Collected Information

MySchoolGist may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes:

  *  **To improve our website**  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our tutorials, design, products and services.
  *  **To personalize user experience**  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  *  **To improve customer service**  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  *  **To send periodic emails**  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If user decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the user would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or user may contact us via our Site.

### How Do We Protect Your Information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

### Do We Disclose Any Information to Outside Parties?

We do not sell, trade, or rent users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

### Third Party Websites

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Google Adsense**  
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.myschoolgist.com.ng. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.myschoolgist.com.ng and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/ "Google ad and content network privacy policy"). MySchoolGist has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

MySchoolGist has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting Us

If you require any more information or have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using the information below.

  * Contact Us [Page](https://www.myschoolgist.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us").
  * Send mail directly [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#4726232a2e29072a3e34242f28282b202e34336924282a)
